<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Fish -->
    <string name="quiz_fish_name">Fish</string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_description">Test how well you know the most common animals!</string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fish</string>
    
    <!-- Fish / Levels -->
    
    <!-- Perch -->
    <string name="quiz_fish_perch_name">Perch</string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_perch_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_perch_description">Perch is a common name for fish of the genus Perca, freshwater gamefish belonging to the family Percidae. The perch, of which there are three species in different geographical areas, lend their name to a large order of vertebrates: the Perciformes, from the Greek perke meaning spotted, and the Latin forma meaning shape. Many species of freshwater gamefish more or less resemble perch, but belong to different genera. In fact, the exclusively saltwater dwelling red drum is often referred to as a red perch, though by definition perch are freshwater fish. Though many fish are referred to as perch as a common name, to be considered a true perch, the fish must be of the family Percidae.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_perch_answers">
    	<item>perch</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_fish_perch_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/perch</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_perch_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- Pike -->
    <string name="quiz_fish_pike_name">Pike / Northern Pike</string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_pike_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_pike_description">The northern pike (Esox lucius), known simply as a pike in Britain, Ireland, most of Canada, and most parts of the USA, (also called jackfish or simply "northern" in the Upper Midwest of the USA and in Manitoba, Canada), is a species of carnivorous fish of the genus Esox (the pikes). They are typical of brackish and fresh waters of the Northern Hemisphere (i.e. holarctic in distribution). Pike grow to a relatively large size: the average length is about 70–120 cm (28–47 in). Even so, lengths of up to 150 cm (59 in) and weights of 25 kg (55 lb) are very rare. The heaviest specimen known so far was caught in 1983 at an abandoned stone quarry in Germany, where the species is called Hecht. This specimen was 147 cm (58 in) long and weighed 31 kg (68 lb). T</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_pike_answers">
    	<item>pike</item>
    	<item>northern pike</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_fish_pike_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Northern_pike</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_pike_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- Pike perch -->
    <string name="quiz_fish_pikeperch_name">Pike perch</string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_pikeperch_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_pikeperch_description">Sander (formerly known as Stizostedion) is a genus of fish in the Percidae (perch) family. They are also known as "pike-perch" because of their resemblance to fish in the unrelated Esocidae (pike) family. Local names for the fish have been the basis for many geographical names, like River Suda in Russia or Saunags village on the Baltic coast.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_pikeperch_answers">
    	<item>pikeperch</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_fish_pikeperch_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/pikeperch</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_pikeperch_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- Salmon -->
    <string name="quiz_fish_salmon_name">Salmon</string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_salmon_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_salmon_description">Salmon /ˈsæmən/ is the common name for several species of fish in the family Salmonidae. Other fish in the same family include trout, char, grayling and whitefish. Salmon are native to tributaries of the North Atlantic (genus Salmo) and Pacific Ocean (genus Oncorhynchus). Many species of salmon have been introduced into non-native environments such as the Great Lakes of North America and Patagonia in South America. Salmon are intensively produced in aquaculture in many parts of the world.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_salmon_answers">
    	<item>salmon</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_fish_salmon_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/salmon</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_salmon_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- Trout -->
    <string name="quiz_fish_trout_name">Trout</string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_trout_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_trout_description">Trout is the name for a number of species of freshwater fish belonging to the genera Oncorhynchus, Salmo and Salvelinus, all of the subfamily Salmoninae of the family Salmonidae. The word trout is also used as part of the name of some non-salmonid fish such as Cynoscion nebulosus, the spotted seatrout or speckled trout.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_trout_answers">
    	<item>trout</item>
    	<item>rainbow trout</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_fish_trout_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/trout</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_trout_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- Burbot -->
    <string name="quiz_fish_burbot_name">Burbot</string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_burbot_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_burbot_description">The burbot (Lota lota) or bubbot is the only gadiform (cod-like) freshwater fish. Also known as mariah, freshwater ling, the lawyer, coney-fish, and (misleadingly) eelpout, the burbot is closely related to the marine common ling and the cusk. It is the only member of the genus Lota.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_burbot_answers">
    	<item>Burbot</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_fish_burbot_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/burbot</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_burbot_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- Bream -->
    <string name="quiz_fish_bream_name">Bream</string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_bream_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_bream_description">"Bream (Listeni/ˈbrɪm/) is a general term for a number of species of freshwater and marine fish belonging to a variety of genera including: Abramis (e.g. A. brama, the common bream), Acanthopagrus, Argyrops, Blicca, Brama, Chilotilapia, Etelis, Lepomis, Gymnocranius, Lethrinus, Nemipterus, Pharyngochromis, Rhabdosargus or Scolopsis.

Although species from all of these genera are called "bream", the term does not imply a degree of relatedness between these species. Fish termed "bream" tend to be narrow, deep bodied species. The name is a derivation of the Middle English word breme, of Old French origin."</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_bream_answers">
    	<item>Bream</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_fish_bream_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/bream</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_bream_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- Roach -->
    <string name="quiz_fish_roach_name">Roach</string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_roach_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_roach_description">The roach (Rutilus rutilus), also known as the common roach, is a fresh and brackish water fish of the Cyprinidae family, native to most of Europe and western Asia. The name "roach" is not unique, but fishes called roach can be any species of the genera Rutilus and Hesperoleucus, depending on locality. The plural of the term is also roach.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_roach_answers">
    	<item>Roach</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_fish_roach_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Common_roach</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_roach_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- Whitefish -->
    <string name="quiz_fish_whitefish_name">Whitefish</string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_whitefish_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_whitefish_description">Coregonus lavaretus is a species of freshwater whitefish, in the family Salmonidae. It is the type species of its genus Coregonus. There is much variation among the European whitefish forms, but in general they have a tapered body, a slightly protruding upper jaw and a fleshy dorsal fin that is typical of the salmon family. The snout is short and tapered, a fact that distinguishes this species from the two other North European Coregonus species, vendace (Coregonus albula) and the introduced peled (Coregonus peled). The former has a protuberant lower jaw while in the latter, the jaws are equal in length. The back is bluish green or brownish, the flanks silvery and the belly white. The fins are dark grey. This fish seldom grows more than 55 cm (22 in) long or exceeds 2 kg (4.4 lb) in weight.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_whitefish_answers">
    	<item>whitefish</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_fish_whitefish_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Coregonus_lavaretus</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_whitefish_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- Herring -->
    <string name="quiz_fish_herring_name">Herring</string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_herring_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_herring_description">Herring are forage fish, mostly belonging to the family Clupeidae. They often move in large schools around fishing banks and near the coast. The most abundant and commercially important species belong to the genus Clupea, found particularly in shallow, temperate waters of the North Pacific and the North Atlantic oceans, including the Baltic Sea, as well as off the west coast of South America. Three species of Clupea are recognised, and provide about 90% of all herrings captured in fisheries. Most abundant of all is the Atlantic herring, providing over half of all herring capture. Fishes called herring are also found in India, in the Arabian Sea, Indian Ocean and Bay of Bengal.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_herring_answers">
    	<item>herring</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_fish_herring_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/herring</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_herring_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- Crab -->
    <string name="quiz_fish_crab_name">Crab</string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_crab_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_crab_description">Crabs are decapod crustaceans of the infraorder Brachyura, which typically have a very short projecting &quot;tail&quot; (abdomen) (Greek: βραχύς / brachys = short, οὐρά / οura = tail), usually entirely hidden under the thorax. They live in all the world\'s oceans, in fresh water, and on land, are generally covered with a thick exoskeleton and have a single pair of claws. Many other animals with similar names – such as hermit crabs, king crabs, porcelain crabs, horseshoe crabs and crab lice – are not true crabs.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_crab_answers">
    	<item>crab</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_fish_crab_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/crab</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_crab_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- Crayfish -->
    <string name="quiz_fish_crayfish_name">Crayfish</string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_crayfish_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_crayfish_description">Crayfish, also known as crawfish, crawdads, freshwater lobsters, or mudbugs, are freshwater crustaceans resembling small lobsters, to which they are related; taxonomically, they are members of the superfamilies Astacoidea and Parastacoidea. They breathe through feather-like gills and are found in bodies of water. Some species are found in brooks and streams where there is fresh water running, while others thrive in swamps, ditches, and rice paddies. Most crayfish cannot tolerate polluted water, although some species such as Procambarus clarkii are hardier. Crayfish feed on living and dead animals and plants.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_crayfish_answers">
    	<item>crayfish</item>
    	<item>crawdad</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_fish_crayfish_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/crayfish</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_crayfish_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- Lobster -->
    <string name="quiz_fish_lobster_name">Lobster</string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_lobster_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_fish_lobster_description">Clawed lobsters comprise a family (Nephropidae, sometimes also Homaridae) of large marine crustaceans. They have long bodies with muscular tails, and live in crevices or burrows on the sea floor. Three of their five pairs of legs have claws, including the first pair, which are usually much larger than the others. Highly prized as seafood, lobsters are economically important, and are often one of the most profitable commodities in coastal areas they populate. Commercially important species include two species of Homarus from the northern Atlantic Ocean, and scampi – the northern-hemisphere genus Nephrops and the southern-hemisphere genus Metanephrops. Although several other groups of crustaceans have the word "lobster" in their names, the unqualified term "lobster" generally refers to the clawed lobsters of the family Nephropidae. Clawed lobsters are not closely related to spiny lobsters or slipper lobsters, which have no claws (chelae), or to squat lobsters. The closest living relatives of clawed lobsters are the reef lobsters and the three families of freshwater crayfish.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_lobster_answers">
    	<item>lobster</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_fish_lobster_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/lobster</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_fish_lobster_facts">
	</string-array>
	
</resources>
