<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Vegetables -->
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_name">Vegetables</string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_description">Test how well you know the most common and healthy vegetables!</string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vegetable</string>
    
    <!-- Vegetables / Levels -->
	
	<!-- Potato -->
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_potato_name">Potato</string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_potato_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_potato_description">The potato is a starchy, tuberous crop from the perennial nightshade Solanum tuberosum L. The word &quot;potato&quot; may refer either to the plant itself or the edible tuber. In the Andes, where the species is indigenous, there are some other closely related cultivated potato species. Potatoes were introduced outside the Andes region approximately four centuries ago, and have since become an integral part of much of the world\'s food supply. It is the world\'s fourth-largest food crop, following maize, wheat, and rice.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_potato_answers">
    	<item>potato</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_vegetables_potato_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/potato</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_potato_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- carrot -->
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_carrot_name">Carrot</string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_carrot_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_carrot_description">The carrot (Daucus carota subsp. sativus) is a root vegetable, usually orange in colour, though purple, red, white, and yellow varieties exist. It has a crisp texture when fresh. The most commonly eaten part of a carrot is a taproot, although the greens are sometimes eaten as well. It is a domesticated form of the wild carrot Daucus carota, native to Europe and southwestern Asia. The domestic carrot has been selectively bred for its greatly enlarged and more palatable, less woody-textured edible taproot. </string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_carrot_answers">
    	<item>carrot</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_vegetables_carrot_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/carrot</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_carrot_facts">
	    <item>Orange</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- Pea -->
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_pea_name">Pea</string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_pea_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_pea_description">The pea is most commonly the small spherical seed or the seed-pod of the pod fruit Pisum sativum. Each pod contains several peas. Pea pods are botanically fruit, since they contain seeds and developed from the ovary of a (pea) flower. The name is also used to describe other edible seeds from the Fabaceae such as the pigeon pea (Cajanus cajan), the cowpea (Vigna unguiculata), and the seeds from several species of Lathyrus.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_pea_answers">
    	<item>pea</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_vegetables_pea_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/pea</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_pea_facts">
	    <item>Green</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- Cabbage -->
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_cabbage_name">Cabbage</string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_cabbage_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_cabbage_description">Cabbage (Brassica oleracea or variants) is a leafy green or purple biennial plant, grown as an annual vegetable crop for its dense-leaved heads. Closely related to other cole crops, such as broccoli, cauliflower, and brussels sprouts, it descends from B. oleracea var. oleracea, a wild field cabbage. Cabbage heads generally range from 0.5 to 4 kilograms (1 to 9 lb), and can be green, purple and white. It is a multi-layered vegetable.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_cabbage_answers">
    	<item>cabbage</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_vegetables_cabbage_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/cabbage</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_cabbage_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- cucumber -->
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_cucumber_name">Cucumber</string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_cucumber_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_cucumber_description">Cucumber (Cucumis sativus) is a widely cultivated plant in the gourd family, Cucurbitaceae. It is a creeping vine that bears cylindrical fruits that are used as culinary vegetables. There are three main varieties of cucumber: slicing, pickling, and burpless. Within these varieties, several different cultivars have emerged. The cucumber is originally from Southern Asia, but now grows on most continents. Many different varieties are traded on the global market.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_cucumber_answers">
    	<item>cucumber</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_vegetables_cucumber_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/cucumber</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_cucumber_facts">
	    <item>Green</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- onion -->
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_onion_name">Onion</string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_onion_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_onion_description">The onion (Allium cepa L.) (Latin \'cepa\' = onion), also known as the bulb onion or common onion, is used as a vegetable and is the most widely cultivated species of the genus Allium. This genus also contains several other species variously referred to as onions and cultivated for food, such as the Japanese bunching onion (A. fistulosum), the Egyptian onion (A. ×proliferum), and the Canada onion (A. canadense).</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_onion_answers">
    	<item>onion</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_vegetables_onion_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/onion</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_onion_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- tomato -->
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_tomato_name">Tomato</string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_tomato_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_tomato_description">The tomato is the edible, often red fruit/berry of the nightshade Solanum lycopersicum, commonly known as a tomato plant. The species originated in the South American Andes and its use as a food originated in Mexico, and spread throughout the world following the Spanish colonization of the Americas. Its many varieties are now widely grown, sometimes in greenhouses in cooler climates.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_tomato_answers">
    	<item>tomato</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_vegetables_tomato_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/tomato</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_tomato_facts">
	    <item>It\'s red.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- rhubarb -->
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_rhubarb_name">Rhubarb</string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_rhubarb_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_rhubarb_description">Rhubarb (Rheum rhabarbarum) is a species of plant in the family Polygonaceae. It is a herbaceous perennial growing from short, thick rhizomes. It produces large leaves that are somewhat triangular, with long fleshy petioles. and small flowers grouped in large compound leafy greenish-white to rose-red inflorescences. Grows during the summer. Especially popular on pies or as a jam.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_rhubarb_answers">
    	<item>rhubarb</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_vegetables_rhubarb_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/rhubarb</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_rhubarb_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- redish -->
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_redish_name">redish</string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_redish_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_redish_description">The radish (Raphanus sativus) is an edible root vegetable of the Brassicaceae family that was domesticated in Europe in pre-Roman times. Radishes are grown and consumed throughout the world, being mostly eaten raw as a crunchy salad vegetable. They have numerous varieties, varying in size, flavor, color and the length of time they take to mature.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_redish_answers">
    	<item>redish</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_vegetables_redish_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/radish</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_redish_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- bean -->
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_bean_name">Bean</string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_bean_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_bean_description">Bean is a common name for large plant seeds of several genera of the family Fabaceae (alternately Leguminosae) which are used for human or animal food.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_bean_answers">
    	<item>bean</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_vegetables_bean_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/bean</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_bean_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- pepper -->
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_pepper_name">Pepper</string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_pepper_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_pepper_description">Bell pepper, also known as sweet pepper or a pepper (in the United Kingdom, Canada and Ireland) and capsicum /ˈkæpsɨkəm/ (in India, Pakistan, Bangladesh, Australia, Singapore and New Zealand), is a cultivar group of the species Capsicum annuum. Cultivars of the plant produce fruits in different colors, including red, yellow, orange, green, chocolate/brown, vanilla/white, and purple. Bell peppers are sometimes grouped with less pungent pepper varieties as "sweet peppers." Peppers are native to Mexico, Central America and northern South America. The ribs and seeds inside bell peppers may be consumed, but some find the taste to be bitter.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_pepper_answers">
    	<item>pepper</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_vegetables_pepper_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bell_pepper</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_pepper_facts">
	    <item>It\'s red.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- pumpkin -->
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_pumpkin_name">Pumpkin</string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_pumpkin_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_pumpkin_description">A pumpkin is a cultivar of the squash plant, most commonly of Cucurbita pepo, that is round, with smooth, slightly ribbed skin and deep yellow to orange coloration. The thick shell contains the seeds and pulp. Some exceptionally large cultivars of squash with similar appearance have also been derived from Cucurbita maxima. Specific cultivars of winter squash derived from other species, including C. argyrosperma, and C. moschata, are also sometimes called "pumpkin". In New Zealand and Australian English, the term "pumpkin" generally refers to the broader category called winter squash elsewhere.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_pumpkin_answers">
    	<item>pumpkin</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_vegetables_pumpkin_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/pumpkin</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_pumpkin_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- garlic -->
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_garlic_name">Garlic</string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_garlic_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_garlic_description">Allium sativum, commonly known as garlic, is a species in the onion genus, Allium. Its close relatives include the onion, shallot, leek, chive, and rakkyo. With a history of human use of over 7,000 years, garlic is native to central Asia, and has long been a staple in the Mediterranean region, as well as a frequent seasoning in Asia, Africa, and Europe. It was known to Ancient Egyptians, and has been used for both culinary and medicinal purposes.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_garlic_answers">
    	<item>garlic</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_vegetables_garlic_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/garlic</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_garlic_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- beetroot -->
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_beetroot_name">Beetroot</string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_beetroot_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_beetroot_description">The beetroot is the taproot portion of the beet plant, also known in North America as the table beet, garden beet, red or golden beet, or informally simply as the beet. It is several of the cultivated varieties of beet (Beta vulgaris) grown for their edible taproots and their greens.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_beetroot_answers">
    	<item>beetroot</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_vegetables_beetroot_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/beetroot</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_beetroot_facts">
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- marrow -->
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_marrow_name">Marrow</string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_marrow_hint"></string>
    <string name="quiz_vegetables_marrow_description">Cucurbita (Latin for gourd) is a genus of herbaceous vine in the gourd family Cucurbitaceae, also known as cucurbits, native to the Andes and Mesoamerica. Five species are grown worldwide for their edible fruit, variously known as squash, pumpkin, or gourd depending on species, variety, and local parlance, and seeds. First cultivated in the Americas before being brought to Europe after the discovery of the New World, plants in the genus Cucurbita are important sources of human food, beverages, and oil. Other kinds of gourd, also called bottle-gourds, are native to Africa and belong to the genus Lagenaria, which is in the same family and subfamily as Cucurbita but in a different tribe. These gourds are used as utensils or vessels.</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_marrow_answers">
    	<item>marrow</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="quiz_vegetables_marrow_link">http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cucurbita</string>
	<string-array name="quiz_vegetables_marrow_facts">
	</string-array>

</resources>
